Lucy Kroll Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Lucy Kroll Papers 1908-1998 (bulk 1950-1990)
MSS78576
Kroll, Lucy
308,350 items
877 containers plus 19 oversize
356 linear feet
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Literary and talent agent. Contracts, correspondence, financial records, notes, photographs, printed matter, and scripts relating to the Lucy Kroll Agency which managed the careers of numerous clients in the literary and entertainment fields.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Braithwaite, E. R. (Edward Ricardo); Davis, Ossie.; Dee, Ruby.; Donehue, Vincent J., 1915-1966.; Fields, Dorothy, 1905-1974.; Foote, Horton.; Gish, Lillian, 1893-1993.; Glass, Joanna M.; Graham, Martha.; Hagen, Uta, 1919-2004.; Hayes, Helen, 1900-1993.; Jones, James Earl.; Kroll family.; Kroll, Lucy.; Kübler-Ross, Elisabeth.; Petrie, Daniel.; Petrie, Dorothea G.; Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967.; Stanley, Kim.; Teichmann, Howard.; Weaver, Fritz, 1926-2016.
Organizations
Lucy Kroll Agency.
Subjects
Literary agents.; Theatrical agents.
Occupations
Literary agents.; Talent agents.
Provenance
The papers of Lucy Kroll, literary and talent agent, were given to the Library of Congress by Kroll in 1969. Additions were given by her between 1977 and 1995. A bequest of further material was made in 1997.
Additional Guides
The Lucy Kroll Papers are described in Library of Congress Information Bulletin, vol. 29, no. 5 (5 February 1970) and in Library of Congress Acquisitions: Manuscript Division, 1994-1995, pp. 93, 116, 132.
Transfers
Items have been transferred from the Manuscript Division to other custodial divisions of the Library. Sound and video recordings have been transferred to the Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Recorded Sound Division. Some posters have been transferred to the Prints and Photographs Division. All transfers are identified in these divisions as part of the Lucy Kroll Papers.
Access and Restrictions
The papers of Lucy Kroll are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1909, July 3 Born, Brooklyn, N.Y.
1933 B.A., Hunter College, New York, N.Y.
1935 M.A., School for the Stage, New York, N.Y. Cofounder, American Actors Company, New York, N.Y.
1939 Married Nathan Kroll (divorced 1974)
1940 1944 Story analyst, Warner Brothers Studio Cofounder, Hollywood Theatre Alliance and Hollywood Music Alliance, Hollywood, Calif.
1944 Instructor and faculty advisor, Hunter College, New York, N.Y.
1945 Agent, Sam Jaffe Agency, New York, N.Y., branch
1947 Established Lucy Kroll Agency, New York, N.Y.
1985 Member, Hall of Fame, Hunter College, New York, N.Y.
1993 Received Living Legacy Award, Women's International Center, San Diego, Calif.
1994 Sold Lucy Kroll Agency to Barbara Hogenson
1997, Mar. 14 Died, Glendale, Mass.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of Lucy Kroll (1909-1997) span the years 1908-1998, with the bulk of the material dating from 1950 to 1990. The papers are organized in the following series: Client File, Miscellany, Office File, and Oversize.
The Client File forms the largest part of the papers. The Lucy Kroll Agency managed the careers of numerous clients in the fields of dance, journalism, literature, motion pictures, music, poetry, psychology, science, sociology, television, and theater. The amount of material for each client is uneven. It ranges from one folder to eighty-two boxes depending on the client's success and longevity with the agency. Therefore, not all types of material are found in every client's file. Typical material includes contracts, referred to as representation agreements, between the client and the Lucy Kroll Agency as well as work contracts between the clients and their employers; incoming and outgoing correspondence between the agency, the clients, and employers; and notes written primarily by Lucy Kroll during negotiations on behalf of her clients. Many files contain financial records such as royalty statements or box office receipts. Also present is publicity material in the form of photographs, playbills, and press clippings. Files of the theatrical clients often include scripts of plays they were considering or in which they appeared. Files of other clients might include various forms of their writings, such as typescripts or printing proofs. Some clients' files contain material called submissions, a process by which the agency submits an actor's name in response to a general casting call by a producer.
The Client File documents the association between Lucy Kroll and her clients. In most cases it went beyond a business arrangement and developed into a deep friendship and mentoring relationship. Kroll often handled the personal affairs of her clients, including financial support and medical care. Notable clients included E. R. (Edward Ricardo) Braithwaite, Ruby Dee and Ossie Davis, Vincent J. Donehue, Lillian Gish, Joanna M. Glass, Martha Graham, Uta Hagen, Helen Hayes, Dorothy Fields (estate of), Horton Foote, Elisabeth Kübler-Ross, James Earl Jones, Daniel and Dorothea G. Petrie, Carl Sandburg, Kim Stanley, Howard Teichmann, and Fritz Weaver.
The Miscellany series contains family papers, material for Kroll's unfinished memoirs, and scripts. The family papers include correspondence with family and personal friends, drama school notes, and household papers. The memoirs section consists entirely of tributes from friends and colleagues which Kroll intended to incorporate into her memoirs. The scripts do not have an identifiable association with any of her clients but may have been under consideration for various projects.
The Office File documents the operations of the Lucy Kroll Agency. Included are daily appointment books, material relating to national and international business trips, financial records, notes, and items relating to prospective clients and projects. Incoming and outgoing correspondence records negotiations with other literary and talent agencies, as well as with publishers, studios, theaters, producers, and various professionals in the literary and entertainment fields. The “deal memoranda file” served the office staff as a quick reference source for the terms of each client's contracts. A Christmas cards and gifts section documents the many “extras” that Kroll extended to clients she considered especially important.
Organization of the Papers
The collection is arranged in four series:
Client File, 1916-1998
Miscellany, 1908-1997
Office File, 1938-1996
Oversize, 1948-1988
Container List
- Client File, 1916-1998 (Box 1-736)
  Contracts, correspondence, financial records, notes, photographs, printed material, and scripts.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of client and therein alphabetically by title of work or type of material and chronologically therein.
  - Aannestad, Elling, 1974, undated (Box 1)
  - Abrahams, Evelyn, 1988, undated
  - Adamic, Louis, 1956-1957, undated
  - Adamo, Jane, 1986
  - Adams, Armenta, 1960-1961, undated
  - Adato, Michelle, 1985, undated
  - Adato, Perry Miller, 1977-1989, undated For additional material see Containers 630-631, Works about Sandburg, (2 folders)
  - Adizes, Ichak, 1989-1990, undated
  - Aleichem, Sholom See Container 703, Waife-Goldberg, B. Z.
  - Alexander, Jane, 1965, 1992-1995, undated
  - Alexander, John, 1951
  - Alfred, William
    - Agamemon
      - Contracts, 1953-1958
      - Correspondence, 1954-1958, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1955, undated
      - Notes, 1954-1958, undated
      - Script, 1953
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1956-1958
      - Notes and printed matter, 1955-1958, undated
    - The Runaways, 1956-1957, undated (Box 2)
  - Allan, Lewis See Container 28, Blankfort, Henry
  - Allbritton, Louise, 1950
  - Allen, Chet
    - Contracts, 1951-1952, (3 folders)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1953, undated, (5 folders)
    - Notes, 1952-1953, undated
    - Photographs
      - 1952, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 3)
      - Undated
    - Printed matter, 1951-1969, undated
  - Aller, Judith, 1984, undated
  - Aller, Victor See Container 705, Waxman, Franz
  - Allison, Karl, 1979
  - Allport, Carolyn
    - Contracts, 1986-1988, undated
    - Correspondence, 1986-1989, undated, (3 folders)
    - Notes, 1986-1988, undated
    - Printed matter, 1986-1989, undated
  - Allyn, William, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Altman, Lawrence K.
    - AIDS (disease), 1985, undated
    - Artificial heart experiments, 1984-1985, undated
    - Baboon heart experiment, 1984
    - Microsurgery, 1981
    - Miscellany, 1978-1990, undated
    - Reagan, Ronald, surgeries, 1985-1987
    - Who Goes First?
      - Contracts and copyright, 1981-1987, undated
      - Correspondence, 1974-1990, undated, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1978-1989, undated
      - Notes, 1976-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5)
      - Printed matter, 1979-1989, undated
  - Altschuler, Richard W., 1965-1966, undated
  - Anderson, Alexandra C., 1981, undated
  - Anderson, Esther
    - Contracts, 1984
    - Correspondence, 1982-1987, undated
    - Miscellany, 1984, undated
    - Notes, 1982-1987, undated
    - Printed matter, 1982-1985, undated
  - Anderson, George E., 1985-1986, undated
  - Anderson, John M., 1982
  - Anderson, Paul, 1951
  - Anderson, Rex, 1967-1969, undated
  - Anderson, Robert, 1962-1968, undated (Box 6)
  - Anderson, Sarah Pia, 1984-1990, undated
  - André, Jill, 1975, undated
  - Andre, Susan, 1975-1979, undated
  - Andryszcak, Ales, 1965-1966
  - Antonio, Lou, 1958
  - Anthony, Joseph
    - Contracts, 1946-1947
    - Correspondence, 1946-1948, undated, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1946-1947, undated
  - Appel, Benjamin, 1959-1960, undated
  - Apstein, Theodore, 1963-1964, undated
  - Aranha, Ray
    - Correspondence, 1976-1991
    - The Coup, 1979
    - City of Hope, 1990
    - The Estate, 1976-1989
    - Fences, 1985-1986, undated
    - Henry IV, 1993, undated
    - Married People, 1989-1991, undated
    - My Sister, My Sister, 1985-1986
    - National Playwrights Conference, Waterford, Conn., 1989
    - Notes, 1976-1989, undated
    - Orphans and Cannibals, 1984-1986, undated (Box 7)
    - The Piano Lesson, 1993
    - Photographs and printed matter, 1989, undated
    - Snow Pressings, 1979-1980, undated
    - Sons and Fathers of Sons, 1983, undated
    - Submissions, 1977, 1984-1990, undated, (3 folders)
    - Two Trains Running, 1993
  - Archbold, John D., 1972, undated
  - Arden, Cathy, 1986, undated
  - Arenal, Julie, 1980, undated
  - Aricha, Amos
    - Hour of the Clown
      - Contracts, 1978
      - Correspondence, 1978-1983, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1978-1983, undated (Box 8)
      - Printed matter, 1978-1982, undated
    - Journey Toward Death
      - Contracts, 1980-1982
      - Correspondence, 1980-1984, undated
      - Notes, 1980-1984, undated
      - Page proofs, undated
      - Printed matter, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1979-1985
      - Financial records, 1979-1990, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1978-1986, undated
    - Phoenix, 1978-1981, undated
  - Arnold, Eve
    - Correspondence, 1976-1996, undated
    - Notes, 1985-1990, undated
    - Printed matter, 1977-1991 (Box 9)
  - Arnold, Kenneth
    - The Barber Shop, 1979-1981, undated
    - Childish Things, 1980 See also same container, She Also Dances
    - Gloria Vivaldi, 1980-1981, undated
    - House of Bedlam
      - Correspondence, 1976-1980, undated
      - Notes, 1977-1978, undated
      - Printed matter, 1976-1979, undated
      - Script, 1978
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1978-1982, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1978-1979, undated
    - She Also Dances See also same container, Childish Things
      - Contracts, 1979-1980
      - Correspondence, 1979-1985, undated
      - Notes, 1979-1982, undated
      - Printed matter, 1979
    - Why Haven't We Seen the Whole Earth? 1978-1981, undated
    - With Child, 1981, undated (Box 10)
  - Arnold, Lisa, 1986
  - Aronson, Alvin, 1956-1962, undated
  - Arno, Sig, undated
  - Arrabal, Fernando, 1969
  - Arthur, Sherwood See Container 559, Pletzke, Marvin
  - Asermely, Al, 1965, undated
  - Ashlock, Rex, 1989-1991, undated
  - Asner, Edward
    - Contracts, 1957-1959
    - Correspondence, 1957-1959, undated
    - Notes, 1957-1959, undated
    - Photograph, undated
    - Printed matter, 1957-1959, undated
  - Auerbach, George, 1958, undated
  - August, Bille, 1988, undated
  - Ayer, Eleanor, 1957-1958, undated
  - Ayler, Ethel, undated
  - Baer, Gwen, 1990, undated
  - Baer, Jean
    - Associated Press, 1966-1967, undated
    - Follow Me, 1965-1969, undated
    - For Love and Money, 1968-1970, undated
    - Handbook for Publicity and Public Relations, 1970, undated
    - Miscellany, 1966-1971, undated
    - The Second Wife
      - Contracts, 1970-1972, undated
      - Correspondence, 1968-1977, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1969-1975, undated
      - Printed matter, 1971-1972, undated (Box 11)
  - Bailey, Peter John, 1982
  - Bain, Conrad
    - Contracts, 1983-1986
    - Correspondence, 1979-1987, undated
    - Country Cops, 1986, undated
    - “Different Strokes,” 1982-1986, undated
    - Miscellany, 1986, undated
    - Notes, 1980-1987, undated, (2 folders)
  - Bainter, Fay
    - Contracts, 1947-1953
    - Correspondence
      - 1944-1948, (3 folders)
      - 1949-1954, undated, (4 folders) (Box 12)
    - Notes, 1948-1952, undated
    - Printed matter, 1949-1951, undated
  - Bakshi, Ralph, 1977-1981, undated
  - Baldwin, Peter
    - Contracts, 1958
    - Correspondence, 1957-1959, undated
    - Notes and photographs, 1958-1959, undated
    - Printed matter, 1958-1959, undated
  - Balfour, Katherine, 1957-1958, undated
  - Bank, Mirra, 1976, 1984, undated
  - Banks, Danny, 1977, 1983, undated
  - Barahal, Hyman S., 1967, 1975
  - Barclift, Nelson, 1956, undated (Box 13)
  - Bardwick, Judith M.
    - Danger in the Comfort Zone, 1991
    - Earn It
      - Correspondence, 1990
      - Notes, 1990, undated
    - The Plateauing Trap
      - Contracts, 1985-1987
      - Correspondence, 1982-1988, undated, (3 folders)
      - Drafts
        - 1983-1984
        - 1985 (Box 14)
      - Notes, 1984-1989, undated, (2 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1985-1990, undated
  - Barker, Joyce
    - Contracts, 1955-1957
    - Correspondence, 1955-1958, undated, (2 folders)
    - Notes, 1955-1958, undated
    - Photographs and printed matter, 1956-1958, undated
  - Barnes, Cheryl, 1979, undated
  - Barnes, Howard G., 1950-1952, 1966-1971, undated
  - Barnett, Gina, 1986, undated
  - Barnitz, Wirt W., 1968
  - Barreiro, Oliver George, 1991
  - Barry, Leonard
    - Contracts, 1960
    - Correspondence, 1960
    - Notes, 1960, undated
  - Barthel, Joan, 1975
  - Baruch, Dorothy (Box 15)
    - Contracts, 1952-1961, undated, (2 folders)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1965, undated, (6 folders)
    - Notes
      - 1952-1955
      - 1956-1964, undated (Box 16)
    - Printed matter, 1952-1953, undated
  - Bashore, Irene Saras, 1977, 1984-1985, undated
  - Bassat, Judith, 1989-1990, undated
  - Bassett, William H.
    - Contracts, 1960-1964
    - Correspondence, 1959-1964, undated
    - Notes, 1962-1963, undated
    - Printed matter, 1960-1962, undated
  - Battle, Edwin Lewis, 1991, undated
  - Bawtree, Michael, 1971-1972, undated
  - Beach, Rex, 1927, 1938-1939, 1945-1951, 1977-1978, undated
  - Bearden, Romare
    - Contracts, 1968
    - Correspondence
      - 1965-1973
      - 1979, 1987-1996, undated, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Notes, 1965-1988, undated
    - Poster, 1968 See Oversize
    - Printed matter, 1965-1995, undated, (2 folders)
    - Royalty statements, 1969-1973
  - Beavers, Robert, 1989-1991, undated
  - Becker, William, 1952-1956, undated
  - Bedell, Madelon
    - The Alcotts
      - Drafts, 1979
      - Illustrations and notes, undated (Box 18)
      - Uncorrected proof, 1980
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1979-1984, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1979-1981, undated
      - Printed matter, 1975-1986, undated
  - Bedell, Sally See Containers 658-659, Smith, Sally Bedell
  - Beggs, E. Larry, 1956, 1967-1969, undated
  - Beling, Stephanie, and Mauri Small, 1991-1993, undated (Box 19)
  - Bellin, Olga
    - Contracts, 1954-1964, 1970
    - Correspondence, 1953-1984, undated, (4 folders)
    - Notes, 1953-1979, undated, (2 folders)
    - Photographs, 1987, undated See also Oversize, (2 folders)
    - Printed matter
      - 1954-1956
      - 1957-1984, undated, (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Benedict, Pinckney, 1993-1994, undated
  - Benny, Jack, 1965, undated
  - Benson, Linda, 1985
  - Benson, Susan, 1987-1989, undated
  - Bentley, Eric
    - Henry IV, 1952-1956, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts, 1952-1953
      - Correspondence, 1951-1955, 1962-1963, 1973, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1951-1954, undated
      - Printed matter, 1951-1955, undated (Box 21)
    - Philomena Maturano ( Created Equal ), 1951-1955, undated
    - Right You Are
      - Contracts, 1952-1953
      - Correspondence, 1951-1955, undated
      - Notes, 1952-1953, undated
      - Printed matter, 1952-1953, undated
  - Bercovitch, Reuben
    - Hasen, 1975
    - Koba
      - Correspondence, 1974-1976, undated
      - Notes, 1974-1975, undated
      - Script, undated
    - Odette, 1972-1975
    - Winter Rates, 1969-1974, undated
  - Berenberg, Ben Ross, 1946, 1985-1988, undated
  - Berghoff, Herbert
    - The Anderson Trial
      - Contracts, 1959-1960
      - Correspondence, 1959-1960
      - Notes, 1959, undated
      - Photographs, undated
      - Printed matter, 1959-1960, undated (Box 22)
    - The Good God of Manhattan, 1963-1964, undated
    - The Guardsman, 1950-1951
    - Habitation of Dragons, 1963
    - HB Studio, 1956-1965, 1975-1978, 1984-1986, 1995, undated
    - In the Summer House, 1963-1964, undated
    - The Lady's Not for Burning, 1953-1954
    - Les Blancs, 1970-1971
    - Love Is a Many Splendored Thing, 1968, undated
    - Mastermind, 1969-1970, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts, 1951-1958
      - Correspondence, 1950-1972, undated
      - Notes, 1951-1962, undated
      - Printed matter, 1953-1990
    - Poor Murderer, 1975-1976
    - Protective Custody, 1956 (Box 23)
    - A Souvenir from Italy, 1951, undated
    - Television, 1952-1957
    - Tovarich, 1952
    - Waiting for Godot, 1956-1957, 1969
  - Bergman, Hjalmar, 1962-1965, undated
  - Bergman, Peter, 1975-1976, undated
  - Berkman, Leonard, 1979
  - Bern-Campbell, Tonia, 1969-1972, undated
  - Berto, Guiseppe, 1947-1952, undated
  - Berry, John
    - Contracts, 1968-1971
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972
    - Notes, 1968-1971, undated
    - Printed matter, 1964-1970
  - Berson, Hugo D. and Lawrence, 1973, undated
  - Bettis, Valerie, 1945-1947, 1955, undated
  - Biddle, Francis (Box 24)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1972, undated, (2 folders)
    - If This Be Treason, undated
    - Notes, 1965-1972, undated
    - Printed matter, 1960-1968, undated
    - The Trial of William Penn, 1971, undated, (2 folders)
  - Bielinska, Olga See Containers 19-20, Bellin, Olga
  - Bierhaus, Edward G., 1967-1971, undated
  - Billups, Annie, 1986
  - Bimonte, Richard
    - The Big Winner (formerly titled Zi-Zi ), 1954-1955, undated
    - The Bigger They Are, 1967-1968, undated (Box 25)
    - Caviar to a General, 1956
    - Christy Adamo, 1954-1956
    - Don't Call Me Sonny, 1954-1955
    - The Goose at Geneva Falls, 1955-1959
    - Henry Strauss Productions, 1956-1967, undated
    - Miscellany, 1954-1964, undated
    - The Mulberry Push, 1956
  - Birch, Patricia, 1960-1961, undated
  - Bird, Ulmer, 1984, undated
  - Bishop, Conrad, and Elizabeth Fuller
    - Actors Theatre of Louisville, Louisville, Ky., 1985-1986
    - Dakota Bones
      - Correspondence, 1983-1989, undated
      - Miscellany, 1984-1986, undated
      - Script, 1983
    - Double Mortgage, 1982-1986, undated
    - Full Hookup
      - Contracts, 1981-1986
      - Correspondence
        - 1982-1983
        - 1984-1990, undated (Box 26)
      - Notes, 1982-1986, undated
      - Photographs, 1984
      - Printed matter, 1982-1986, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1983-1989
      - Script, 1983
    - Marie Antoinette, 1987-1990, undated
    - Marvels, 1986-1988
    - Mine Alone
      - Contracts, 1989
      - Correspondence, 1988-1992, undated
      - Miscellany, 1989-1990, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1989-1990
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1982-1992, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1981-1991, undated (Box 27)
      - Printed matter, 1982-1988
    - Okiboji
      - Correspondence, 1988-1992, undated
      - Notes, 1988-1992, undated
      - Royalty statements, 1994, undated
      - Script, 1988
    - Smitty's News
      - Contracts, 1985
      - Correspondence, 1985-1988, undated
      - Miscellany, 1985-1986, undated
      - Printed matter, 1986, undated
      - Script, 1985
    - Summer Sisters, 1986-1987, undated
    - Tap Dancer, 1981-1983, undated
    - Wanna, 1979-1987, undated
  - Bishop, Nancy, 1986
  - Blackburn, Clarice, 1953-1956, undated (Box 28)
  - Blackwell, Pamela, 1989-1990
  - Blake, James P.
    - Contracts, 1977-1978
    - Correspondence, 1976-1978, undated
    - Miscellany, 1977-1978, undated See also Oversize
    - Typescript, undated
  - Blankfort, Henry, and Lewis Allan
    - Correspondence, 1946-1950, undated
    - Miscellany, 1947-1949, undated
  - Blankfort, Michael, 1946-1948, 1973-1984, undated
  - Bloch, Daniel, 1985, undated
  - Bloom, Claire, 1989-1991, undated
  - Bloomfield, Don, 1986, undated
  - Bloomfield, Harold J.
    - Contracts, 1973-1982
    - Correspondence
      - 1982
      - 1983-1989, undated, (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Miscellany, 1983, undated
    - Notes, 1976-1988, undated, (5 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1975-1984, undated
    - Royalty statements, 1982-1990
    - Typescripts
      - Draft, undated
      - Final, 1983 (Box 30)
  - Bloomgarden, Henry S., and Malcolm Wells
    - Contracts, 1964
    - Correspondence, 1964-1967
    - Notes and printed matter, 1963-1967
  - Bloomgarden, Lee
    - Dowd, Redfield, and Johnstone, Inc., advertisements, 1951-1952, undated
    - The Human Touch, 1953-1954, undated
    - It's a Gift
      - Contracts, 1947-1949
      - Correspondence, 1947-1952, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1947-1949, undated
    - Jackpot Man, 1955-1956 (Box 31)
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1947-1953, undated
      - Notes, 1951-1952, undated
      - Script outlines, 1951
  - Bluebond-Langer, Myra
    - Miscellany, 1975-1978, undated
    - Typescript, 1975
  - Bochco, Barbara Bosson See Container 32, Bosson, Barbara
  - Boettinger, Henry M., 1971-1973, undated
  - Bogoch, Anne E., 1990
  - Bogart, Humphrey
    - Correspondence, 1944-1949, undated, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1945-1949, undated
  - Bondi, Beula
    - Contracts, 1950
    - Correspondence, 1950-1956, undated
    - Miscellany, 1950-1956, undated
  - Bonnet, James (Box 32)
    - Miscellany, 1965-1977, 1994, undated
    - Script, 1981
  - Borden, Frederick, 1984, undated
  - Borel, Helen, 1973, 1984, undated
  - Born-Bornstein, Roman, 1974
  - Bosson, Barbara, 1992
  - Botsford, Ward, 1979-1981, undated
  - Bowser, Kenneth
    - In a Shallow Grave
      - Correspondence, 1987-1990, undated
      - Notes, 1987-1989, undated
      - Printed matter, 1987-1988, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1988-1991, undated
      - Notes, 1988-1990, undated
      - Printed matter, 1987-1990
    - Preston Sturges, The Rise and Fall of an American Dreamer, 1990, undated
    - The Sunlight Dialogues